- ♪
♪
[Squishy barks]
[软糖犬吠]
- Ugh!
呃！
I did not sleep a wink last night.
我昨晚一整夜都没合眼。
Okay, this is the part where you ask me why.
好吧，这时候你应该问我为什么。
[cereal crunching]
[麦片咀嚼声]
I thought you'd never ask.
我以为你永远不会问呢。
Okay, well, Ms. Tassinari gave yet another Glee Club solo
好吧，嗯，塔西纳里女士又给了格丽俱乐部独唱的机会给布鲁克林，而不是我。
to Brooklyn and not me.
这就是你没睡的原因？
- That's why you didn't sleep?
哇。我们都有自己的烦恼。
Wah. We've all got problems.
哇。我们都有自己的问题。
Try tossing and turning all night because you have
试着整夜辗转反侧，因为你有一种
the horrible feeling you didn't ace your science test.
糟糕的感觉，你没有在科学考试中取得好成绩。
- Not acing a test? Talk about a wah.
考试没考好？那真是哇了。
- Hey, it's a slippery slope.
嘿，这是个滑坡。
First, you don't ace one, then another.
首先，你没考好一次，然后又是一次。
Before you know it, the perfect GPA you've worked so hard for
在你意识到之前，你为之努力了那么久的完美GPA
is hopping on the turd boat to fail town!
正搭乘着失败之船前往失败小镇！
- Yeah. Just like all my hard work with Taylie.
是啊。就像我对Taylie所做的所有努力一样。
Like, I've been not talking to her for weeks,
就像，我已经几周没和她说话了，
and she still hasn't talked to me.
而且她还是没跟我说话。
- I'm confused. Do you wanna talk to her or not?
- 我糊涂了。你是想跟她说话还是不想？
- Of course I wanna talk to her.
- 当然我想跟她说话。
That's why I'm not talking to her.
这就是为什么我不跟她说话。
- Maybe you need to change your approach.
- 也许你需要改变一下你的方法。
- Wait, so you're saying I gotta talk to her?
- 等等，你的意思是我得跟她说话？
But I got nothing to talk about.
但我没什么可说的。
[Squishy barks]
[Squishy 汪汪叫]
- Well, all your problems pale
- 好吧，你所有的烦恼跟我的一比都显得微不足道：那就是Boulder-dash。
in comparison to mine: the Boulder-dash.
这是学校里最远的两个点
It's the farthest two points at the school
that any student has to travel,
任何学生都必须穿越这段距离，
and I have to do it between second and third period.
而我必须在第二和第三节课之间完成这段路程。
Ugh. [voice breaks] It's nearly impossible.
呃。[声音哽咽]这几乎是不可能的。
- Dude, are you crying?
- 伙计，你在哭吗？
- No. It's my Vidalia onions.
- 没有。是我的维达利亚洋葱。
If I'm late for cooking class one more time,
如果我再有一次迟到烹饪课，
Mr. Wigglesworth is gonna give me detention.
威格斯沃斯先生会让我留堂。
- Well, maybe you'd make it on time
- 嗯，也许如果你不拖着所有那些食物
if you weren't lugging all that food
和——我不知道——一个铸铁煎锅。
and--I don't know-- a cast-iron skillet.
还有——我不知道——一个铸铁煎锅。
- [gasps] My baby is perfectly seasoned!
我的宝贝已经完美地调味了！
I shall not cook without her.
没有她我绝不做饭。
- [sighs] - Kids, what have we told you
孩子们，我们告诉过你们什么
about not paying enough attention to Squishy?
关于没有足够关注Squishy的事情？
[together] That when we don't,
当我们不关注他时，
he acts out, and destroys your stuff.
他会闹情绪，还会毁掉你们的东西。
- Exactly.
没错。
And I can't even find the other one.
而且我甚至找不到另一个。
- Hey, why have you kids been ignoring Squishy?
嘿，为什么你们这些孩子一直忽视Squishy？
Clearly, he needs his play time.
显然，他需要玩耍的时间。
- Sorry. We've all been
- 对不起。我们都忙于学校的事情。
too busy with things at school.
- 嗯，你不能用学校的事作为不照顾你的狗的借口。
- Well, you can't use school
你必须认真对待你的Squishy责任。
as an excuse not to take care of your dog.
- 找到了你的另一只拖鞋，汤姆。
You have to take your Squishy responsibilities seriously.
- 哦。至少他没咬那只，对吧？
- Found your other slipper, Tom.
[两人轻笑]
- Oh. Well, at least he didn't chew that one, huh?
[清嗓子] - [叹气]
[both chuckle]
- 但他确实在里面留下了东西。
[clears throat] - [sighs]
- [惊呼] Squishy！
- But he did leave something in it.
但是他在里面留下了一些东西。
- [gasps] Squishy!
是Squishy！
- Yes! Yes, it is.
是的！是的，就是它。
- Ew. - Ugh!
呃。
[upbeat music]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[whistling]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 一、二、三、四！ ♪ ♪ 嘿！ ♪
[cheerful music]
【欢快的音乐】
- Hey, guys! Wish me luck.
嘿，伙计们！祝我好运。
Ms. Tassinari said she's gonna be giving out
塔西纳里女士说她会在春季演唱会上再给出一个独唱机会。
one more solo for the Spring Sing.
也许会是我。
Maybe it'll be me.
也许我考试得了满分。
- And maybe I aced my test.
也许我会想到和泰莉聊些什么。
- And maybe I'll think of something to talk to Taylie about.
【金属撞击声】
[metal clanging]
【叹气】我知道那撞击声。
- [sighs] I know that clanging.
那是9点58分的巨石冲刺。
- It's the 9:58 Boulder-dash.
这是9:58的巨石冲刺。
- [screaming] Coming through, people!
大家让开，我来了！
Coming through!
让开！
Make a hole, people!
大家让开！
I'm on the Boulder-dash!
我在巨石冲刺上！
[school bell rings] The tardy bell!
迟到铃响了！
Mr. Wigglesworth, no!
Wigglesworth先生，不！
[gasps]
吸气声
- You are tardy! Again!
你迟到了！又迟到了！
- I'm sorry, I--
对不起，我——
- If you don't have a legitimate excuse,
如果你没有正当理由，
it's detention for you!
你就要被留堂了！
- I have a legitimate excuse--
我有正当理由——
- And I don't want to hear any balderdash
我不想听任何关于Boulder-dash的胡说八道。哇。
about the Boulder-dash. Wah.
好吧，我——
- Okay, well, I--
（手机铃声）
[cell phone chimes]
Harper先生，
- Mr. Harper,
你的手机上有什么比留堂更有趣的东西吗？
is there something more interesting
抱歉，我的狗出了点事故。
on your phone than detention?
事故？
- Sorry, my dog had an accident.
对不起，我的狗出了点事。
- An accident?
出事了？
Well, that sounds serious.
那听起来挺严重的。
- It is serious.
确实很严重。
- [gasps] How serious?
真的吗？有多严重？
- Very serious.
非常严重。
[sniffles] My dad's been texting me all morning.
（抽泣）我爸爸整个早上都在给我发短信。
That's why I'm tardy!
这就是我迟到的原因！
- [stammers] No tardy.
（结巴）没有迟到。
No tardy. - [weeping]
没有迟到。（哭泣）
[rock music]
- Oh, Nicky!
- 哦，Nicky！
We just wanted to say we're so sorry.
我们只是想说我们非常抱歉。
- I know.
- 我知道。
- [sighs] - [weakly] I know.
- [叹气] - [虚弱地] 我知道。
- We hope he gets better soon.
- 我们希望他很快好起来。
- I know. [sniffles]
- 我知道。[抽泣]
I know.
我知道。
- Poor Squishy!
- 可怜的Squishy！
- Squishy? What's wrong with Squishy?
- Squishy？Squishy怎么了？
- Oh... - They don't know.
[whispers] They don't know.
- Well, tell us! Tell us!
- [sighs]
Will you guys excuse me for one second?
- Of course.
- [sighs] Oh! [sniffles]
Oh, thank you.
[inhales deeply]
- What's wrong with Squishy?
- [voice breaks] Nothing.
没什么。
[normal voice] Absolutely nothing.
绝对没什么。
- So what's wrong?
那到底怎么了？
- Yeah, did you get detention?
是啊，你被留堂了吗？
- Nope. None. Absolutely none.
没有。一点也没有。
- Then what's going on? Tell us!
那到底发生了什么？告诉我们！
- All right.
好吧。
So I was tardy again.
所以我又迟到了。
I may have made up a teeny-tiny little excuse
我可能编了一个小小的借口
about Squishy breaking his leg.
关于Squishy摔断了腿。
- [gasps] - And his tail.
- [惊讶] - 还有他的尾巴。
- [gasps] - And his head.
- [惊讶] - 还有他的头。
- [gasps] - And I used
- [惊讶] - 而我用了
my chopped Vidalia onions
我切好的维达利亚洋葱
to make it look like I was crying.
来制造我哭泣的假象。
- Wait, Nicky, how could you do this?
- 等等，尼基，你怎么能这样做？
- Actually, I just panicked.
- 实际上，我只是慌了。
And once the first one came out,
而一旦第一个谎言说出口，
they all just kept coming out like a river of lies.
它们就像谎言的河流一样源源不断。
But, oh, the best part is, no tardy, no detention,
但，哦，最好的部分是，没有迟到，没有留堂，
and hugs from girls.
还有女生的拥抱。
- I can't believe this. I've heard enough.
我简直不敢相信。我已经听够了。
- Nicky, you can't just play
Nicky，你不能这样利用别人的同情心；这是不对的。
on people's sympathies like that; it's wrong.
是啊，你最好祈祷真相不要曝光，
- Yeah, and you better hope the truth doesn't come out
否则你整个学年都得关禁闭。
'cause you'll be in detention for the rest of the year.
哦，嘿，快看。
- Oh, hey, check it out.
Dicky终于在和Taylie说话了。
Dicky's finally talking to Taylie.
嗯。不知道他找到了什么话题。
Huh. Wonder what he found to talk about.
还有他的头。
- [weeping] And his head.
还有他的尾巴。
- [gasps] - And his tail.
- [倒抽气] - 还有他的尾巴。
- [gasps] - And his legs.
- [倒抽气] - 还有他的腿。
He's got four of the cutest little casts you've ever seen.
他有四个你见过的最可爱的小石膏。
Maybe someday... [sniffles]
也许有一天... [抽鼻子]
[strained] You can sign them.
[吃力] 你可以给他们签名。
[sobbing]
[啜泣]
- What did you do? I thought you said you heard enough!
- 你做了什么？我以为你说你听够了！
- Yeah, I did. I heard enough to know it would work.
- 是的，我是听够了。我听够了知道这会奏效。
The onions were clutch, dude.
洋葱是关键，伙计。
- Vidalia never fail ya.
- 维达利亚洋葱从未让你失望。
- No! No fist-bumping!
不！不要碰拳！
This is Squishy we're talking about.
我们说的是Squishy。
- I can't believe you two.
我真不敢相信你们两个。
Using a fake story about our beloved dog
用我们心爱的狗的假故事
to get what you want?
来得到你们想要的东西？
I, for one, would never stoop so low.
我，就我个人而言，绝不会这么卑鄙。
- Ricky, I've got some good news for you.
Ricky，我有好消息告诉你。
You got a 99 on your test. Top of the class!
你考试得了99分。全班第一！
- 99? [high-pitched] Toot-toot!
99分？[高音]嘟嘟！
- Ooh, tootin' your own horn, huh?
哦，自己吹喇叭，是吧？
- No! That's the toot-toot
不！那是粪船离开港口的嘟嘟声！
of the turd boat leaving the harbor!
你需要让我重考这次测试。
You need to let me retake this test.
我需要我的100分。
I need my 100.
Ricky，你知道我只允许在极端情况下重考。
- Ricky, you know I only allow retakes
我的狗！
under extreme circumstances.
你在开玩笑吗？
- My dog!
Dawn，这是无受害者的犯罪。
- Are you kidding me?
而且，这不会影响到你。
- Dawn, it's a victimless crime.
你总是这么说，但不知怎么的，它总是有影响。
- And besides, it's not gonna affect you.
你的行为也影响我们，你知道吗？我们也有感情。
- You say that all the time, and yet somehow it always does.
你总是这么说，但不知怎么的，它总是会影响到我。
- Your actions affect us too, you know? We have feelings.
你的行为也会影响到我们，你知道吗？我们也有感情。
- Nice try, but the Vidalias...
尝试不错，但维达利亚...
just failed ya.
让你失望了。
- [sighs]
叹气
You over-onioned, dude.
你洋葱加多了，伙计。
[rock music]
我决定谁将获得
- And I've decided who will get
我们...♪春之歌♪的最后独唱
the final solo for our... ♪ Spring Sing ♪
咯咯笑
[giggles] Dawn Harper...
道恩·哈珀...
- Yes! - Was my first choice
- 是的！ - 这是我最初的选择
until I heard the awful news about your dog.
直到我听到了关于你狗狗的糟糕消息。
- No! - That is so sad.
- 不！ - 那真是太伤心了。
And I don't want to put any extra burden on you.
我不想给你增加任何额外的负担。
So I'm giving the solo to Brooklyn.
所以我把独唱机会给了布鲁克林。
- Of course you are.
- 当然你会这么做。
- As a fellow dog owner,
- 作为同样养狗的人，
I know how hard this must be for you.
我知道这对你来说一定很难。
And I'm sure it's hard on your brothers as well.
而且我相信这对你的兄弟们来说也很难。
- It's hitting me now,
- 我现在感受到了，
but it's really about to hit them.
但对他们来说，这真的即将到来。
[rock music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, guys. We heard about Squishy.
嘿，伙计们。我们听说了Squishy的事。
- Yeah. Everybody's texting about him.
是啊。大家都在发短信讨论他。
- Is he gonna be okay?
他会没事的吗？
- [sighs] Look.
（叹气）看。
We know it sounds serious...
我们知道这听起来很严重...
- But it's not as bad as you think.
但没你想的那么糟。
- It's not? - Uh...
不是吗？
[both sobbing]
[两人哭泣]
- No, it's much, much worse!
不，情况要糟糕得多！
- Did you hear that, everybody?
你们听到了吗，各位？
Poor Squishy is much, much worse!
可怜的Squishy情况要糟糕得多！
- [weeping] I could use a hug!
[哭泣] 我需要一个拥抱！
[brothers sobbing]
[兄弟们哭泣]
- Look, Ms. Tassinari,
看，Tassinari女士，
I understand your concerns,
我理解您的担忧，
but I can still do the solo.
但我仍然可以完成独奏。
It's not a burden at all.
这根本不是负担。
- Dawn,
- 晨曦，
you don't have to be tough.
你不必逞强。
We've all heard about poor Squishy.
我们都听说了可怜的Squishy。
- Yeah, about that...
- 是啊，关于那件事...
It's really not as bad as you think.
真的没有你想的那么糟糕。
[cell phones chiming]
[手机铃声]
- [gasps] Oh, no!
- [惊呼] 哦，不！
Sadie just texted that Kipper just posted
Sadie刚刚发短信说Kipper刚刚发布了
that Dicky told Taylie that
说Dicky告诉Taylie
Squishy is worse than we thought.
Squishy的情况比我们想象的还要糟。
all: Aww...
哎呀...
- Will you excuse me for one second?
- 能失陪一下吗？
[piano clangs] Sorry!
[钢琴声]
Hey guys, remember how you promised me
嘿，伙计们，记得你们答应过我
that your Squishy lies wouldn't affect me?
你们的Squishy的谎言不会影响我吗？
- Yeah, how's that going?
- 是啊，那情况如何？
- Not good!
- 不太好！
Everybody's texting what you said
大家都在发你们说的关于Squishy情况更糟的消息，
about Squishy being much worse,
现在Tassinari女士不想
and now Ms. Tassinari doesn't want
让我承担独奏的压力。
to "burden me" with a solo.
不想让我“负担”一个独奏。
- Well, yeah, but you don't get solos anyway.
- 嗯，是的，反正你也得不到独奏。
- I was getting this one! - Congratulations.
- 我本来要得到这个的！ - 恭喜。
- It's nice to get some good news
- 在这所有的Squishy悲剧中间听到一些好消息真好。
in the middle of all this Squishy tragedy.
- 没有悲剧！
- There is no tragedy!
- 你没听说消息吗？
- Haven't you heard the news?
- [叹气]听着，
- [sighs] Listen,
你们需要停止撒谎
you guys need to stop lying
并向所有人坦白
and come clean to everyone
这样我才能重新得到我的独奏。
so that I can get my solo back.
这样我就能拿回我的独奏了。
- But, Dawn, I would lose out on retaking that test.
但是，Dawn，我会失去重新考试的机会。
- Yeah, and I would miss out on Taylie.
是啊，我会错过Taylie。
- And I would get detention.
而我则会受到留校察看的处分。
- Okay, okay. I get it.
好了，好了。我明白了。
You don't have to tell the truth.
你们不必说实话。
But please, for me, go back in there
但请为了我，回到那里
and tell everyone that Squishy made a miraculous recovery.
告诉所有人Squishy奇迹般地康复了。
- Wait, so you want us to lie to get out of a lie?
等等，你是想让我们为了摆脱一个谎言而撒谎吗？
- How low do you want us to go?
你到底想让我们做到什么地步？
- So low that I get my solo.
- 低到我能拿到我的独唱。
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
- Hey, Anne?
- 嘿，Anne？
I know I told the kids to pay more attention to Squishy.
我知道我告诉孩子们要更关注Squishy。
Just in case that doesn't happen, I got him a friend.
只是以防万一那没发生，我给他找了个朋友。
[barking] Oh!
[吠叫] 哦！
- No! You did not get another dog, did you?
- 不！你没又弄来一只狗，对吧？
- No, it's better than a dog.
- 不，这比狗还好。
It's a robot dog.
这是一只机器狗。
[Squishy growls, robot dog whirs]
[Squishy低吼，机器狗嗡嗡作响]
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
- Excuse me.
对不起。
Sorry, I just had to go take care of a little thing.
抱歉，我刚刚不得不去处理一件小事。
So what'd I miss?
那我错过了什么？
- Well, actually, Sadie and Kipper
嗯，实际上，Sadie和Kipper
brought us some very exciting news.
给我们带来了一个非常令人兴奋的消息。
Principal Noonan-- - Was so moved by your tragedy--
Noonan校长--
- That she wants the Booster Club to hold--
被你们的悲剧深深触动--
- Hold a fund-raiser for Squishy.
她想让助威团举办--
- Right. Because she knows--
为Squishy举办一场筹款活动。
- How expensive the vet bills can be.
- 兽医账单可能非常昂贵。
- I got it. And she'd lo--
- 我明白了。她非常——
- Love to help out.
- 愿意帮忙。
- Still got it. Isn't a fun--
- 依然如此。举办一个——
- A fund-raiser a great idea?
- 筹款活动不是个好主意吗？
- Fund-raiser?
- 筹款活动？
Oh, no, no, no, it's-- it's really not necessary.
哦，不，不，不，真的没必要。
In fact, I think you're all going to hear
实际上，我想你们很快都会听到
some very good Squishy news soon.
一些关于Squishy的好消息。
- Oh, well, that would change things
- 哦，那样的话情况就不同了
because I was thinking it would pull more heartstrings
因为我觉得这样更能触动人心
and raise more money for Squishy if you--
并且为Squishy筹集更多资金，如果你——
- You performed a song in front of the whole school!
- 你在全校面前表演一首歌！
- Can't give me one?
- 不能给我一个吗？
- Wait, me perform a song
- 等等，我表演一首歌
in front of the whole school?
在全校面前？
Like a solo?
像独唱那样？
- This would've been such a great chance
- 这本是一个让你脱颖而出的绝佳机会
for you to stand out.
- 但现在这已经不重要了！
- But that doesn't matter anymore!
不重要了？
- It doesn't? - No, the good news is,
- 它不会吗？ - 不会，好消息是，
Squishy seems to be getting better.
Squishy似乎在好转。
- Oh, no, no, no, no!
- 哦，不，不，不，不！
He's not getting better.
他并没有好转。
In fact, I was just saying that to make
事实上，我刚才那么说只是为了让
you all feel better, but he's actually getting worse.
你们都感觉好一点，但他实际上在恶化。
It's really bad.
真的很糟糕。
So about my solo... [weeping]
那么关于我的独奏... [哭泣]
[voice breaks] What should I wear?
[声音哽咽] 我应该穿什么？
[cell phone chimes]
[手机铃声]
- Taylie just texted that Miles said that Dicky
Taylie刚发来短信说Miles提到Dicky
told Mae that Nicky and Ricky have big news about Squishy.
告诉Mae说Nicky和Ricky有关于Squishy的大新闻。
- [wailing] Be right back!
我马上回来！
- So the truth about Squishy is--
所以关于Squishy的真相是——
- [grunts] - Oh!
哦！
- Squishy's worse than ever!
Squishy的情况比以往任何时候都糟！
He actually just came down with...
他实际上刚刚患上了……
woofing cough.
一种叫woofing的咳嗽。
- I've never heard of that.
我从没听说过这个。
- Yeah, well, it's very, very rare.
是的，这非常非常罕见。
In fact, we're having a benefit concert
事实上，我们正在举办一场慈善音乐会
for poor, sick, woofing, bent, little Squishy,
为了可怜的、生病的、咳嗽的、弯曲的小Squishy，
where I will be performing my very first solo!
在那里我将首次进行我的个人表演！
You should all come.
你们都应该来。
- We definitely will.
我们一定会来。
For Squishy! all: For Squishy!
为了Squishy！
- What?
什么？
- Woofing cough? Is that even a real thing,
咳嗽？那真的是个东西吗，
or is this all just a quad thing?
还是这只是个四人组的事情？
- A--a quad thing? - What's that?
四人组的事情？那是什么？
- Well, it's a Mae way of saying,
- 嗯，这是Mae的说法，
"big, fat lie."
"大，胖谎言。"
- Pssh!
- 啧！
Why would I big, fat lie?
我为什么要撒大，胖谎？
I mean, it's not like I made up a disease
我的意思是，我又不是编造了一个疾病
just to sing a solo at a benefit
只是为了在一个慈善活动上独唱
or my brothers made up a broken tail
或者我的兄弟们编造了一个断尾的故事
just to get out of detention
只是为了逃避拘留
or get a hug or get to retake a test.
或是为了得到一个拥抱，或重新考试。
- Yeah, those all sound like quad things.
- 是的，这些听起来都像是quad会做的事。
- [coughing] Big, fat lies!
- [咳嗽声] 大谎话，全是！
- Well, they're not. Gentlemen.
- 不，他们不是。先生们。
Hmph!
哼！
- Well, well, well.
- 哎呀，哎呀，哎呀。
- How the tables have turned.
- 真是风水轮流转啊。
- Looks like my shoe was on the other foot.
- 看来我的鞋穿反了。
- What? That's not the saying, Dicky.
- 什么？那不是那个说法，迪基。
- What saying? My left shoe is on my right foot.
- 什么说法？我的左鞋穿在右脚上。
- There you are.
- 你在这儿。
[together] Principal Noonan!
[齐声] 校长努南！
- I've been looking for you! - You have?
- 我一直在找你！ - 是吗？
- We need to talk about this benefit
- 我们需要谈谈你狗的福利问题。
for your dog, right now.
现在就谈。
- We do? - Yes.
- 是吗？ - 是的。
The whole thing just doesn't feel right.
整个事情感觉不对劲。
- It doesn't? - No!
- 不对劲吗？ - 对！
Broken leg, broken head, broken tail,
断腿，断头，断尾，
and now woofing cough?
现在还有咳嗽？
- It's a thing.
- 这是常有的事。
- I know. My dog had it.
- 我知道。我的狗也得过。
- It's a thing!
- 这是个问题！
- But something still just doesn't feel right.
- 但总感觉有些不对劲。
- Why is she dragging this out so long?
- 她为什么拖这么久？
- We cannot have a benefit without the guest of honor.
- 没有贵宾，我们就不能举办这个活动。
You need to bring Squishy to the school
你需要把Squishy带到学校
so you can sing to him.
这样你就可以给他唱歌了。
- Bring him here? - Exactly.
- 把他带到这里？ - 没错。
We'll see you and that poor little pup here tomorrow.
我们明天在这里等你和那只可怜的小狗。
Dicky, your shoes are on the wrong feet.
Dicky，你的鞋子穿反了。
- She knows my name!
- 她知道我的名字！
[rock music]
♪ ♪
- No one at the benefit is gonna buy this.
- 慈善晚会上没人会买这个。
- Looks good to me.
- 我觉得挺好的。
- Says the guy whose shoes
- 说这话的人，
are still on the wrong feet.
鞋子还穿反了呢。
- It has to work!
- 一定得管用！
- Hey!
- 嘿！
You're playing with Squishy?
你在和Squishy玩吗？
- [nervous laugh] - Yeah!
- [紧张的笑] - 是的！
- Taking our Squishy responsibilities seriously.
我们在认真对待照顾Squishy的责任。
- Like you told us.
就像你告诉我们的那样。
- Why are you wrapping him in gauze?
你为什么用纱布包着他？
- We're not. We found him like this.
我们没有。我们发现他时就这样了。
And we're unwrapping him.
我们正在解开他。
- Okay, this seems like a quad thing.
好吧，这看起来像是四人组的事情。
- When did everybody start saying "a quad thing"?
大家什么时候开始说‘四人组的事情’的？
- Change the subject. - Right.
换个话题。
Hey, Mom, did you hear Dawn is singing a solo
好的。嘿，妈妈，你听说Dawn要在学校的慈善募捐活动中独唱吗？
in a charity fund-raiser for school?
Dawn！独唱？亲爱的，那太棒了！
- Dawn! A solo? Honey, that is wonderful!
Dawn! 独唱？亲爱的，这太棒了！
When is it? Your dad and I are not missing this.
什么时候？我和你爸爸一定不会错过这个。
- You can't come!
你们不能来！
I mean, I'd be nervous if you guys were there.
我是说，如果你们在的话我会很紧张的。
Plus, it's for a totally ridiculous charity.
而且，这是为了一个完全荒谬的慈善机构。
- Really? What charity? - Uh...
真的吗？什么慈善机构？
- Squirrels. - Who are allergic to nuts.
松鼠。
- It's a real problem.
它们对坚果过敏。
- 'Cause that's what they eat. [laughs]
这确实是个问题。
- Yeah, this sounds like a quad thing too.
因为那是它们吃的东西。[笑]
- When did everyone start calling our lies
什么时候大家开始把我们的谎言叫做
"a quad thing"? - Forget about that!
“四人组的事”？
Just help me make this look believable.
别管那个了！
- Hey, kids!
帮我让这个看起来可信点。
I know how busy you've been lately,
嘿，孩子们！
so I got Squishy a friend.
我知道你们最近很忙，
Who's a good girl?
所以我给Squishy找了个朋友。
Who's a good girl, huh?
谁是乖女孩？
[Squishy growls, robot whirs]
谁是乖女孩，嗯？
Now play.
现在玩吧。
- You guys thinking what I'm thinking?
你们是不是在想我正在想的事？
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
♪ ♪
- Squishy's here!
Squishy在这里！
all: Aww.
大家：哎呀。
- Such a brave little fella.
真是个勇敢的小家伙。
- Oh, no, no! - Not too close.
哦，不，不！别靠太近。
- Doctor's orders. - He's highly contagious.
医生的命令。他高度传染。
- Trust me, you do not want woofing cough!
相信我，你不会想得犬吠咳的！
- Yeah. She got it from him.
是啊。她是被他传染的。
- [shrill cough, chuckles]
[尖锐的咳嗽声，轻笑]
[barks]
[吠叫声]
[sheepish laugh]
[尴尬的笑声]
I've got a touch of it.
我有点感染了。
[barking]
[吠叫声]
- [barking]
It really does linger.
它真的会持续很久。
Wow, that is some cast! Can he breathe okay in there?
哇，那个石膏真厉害！他在里面能呼吸吗？
- Oh, sure. Doc left him a little breathing hole.
哦，当然。医生给他留了个呼吸孔。
- And a poop slot.
还有一个排便口。
- Will you excuse us, Principal Noonan?
- 你能原谅我们吗，努南校长？
Little guy needs his rest.
小家伙需要休息。
- Yes. Rest is good.
- 是的。休息是好的。
[coughs, barks]
[咳嗽，吠叫]
- Can you believe all these people
- 你能相信所有这些人
are here to support Squishy? [toy squeaks]
都是来支持斯奎希的吗？[玩具吱吱叫]
- This is for Squishy. [toy squeaking]
- 这是给斯奎希的。[玩具吱吱叫]
Seeing him in that full doggy cast
看到他在那个全副武装的狗狗装里
makes me feel terrible for thinking it was a quad thing.
让我觉得自己之前认为那是四轮车的事感到很糟糕。
Even you wouldn't take it this far.
即使是你也不会做到这个地步。
- Of course we wouldn't.
我们当然不会。
Thanks for your support, Mae.
梅，感谢你的支持。
[louder] And thanks for all of your support!
还有，感谢大家的支持！
Now, Squishy needs his rest.
现在，Squishy需要休息。
- Yeah, he really does. - He's been through so much.
是的，他真的需要。- 他经历了太多。
- Your love is really helping him heal!
你们的爱真的在帮助他恢复！
I don't really believe they believed us.
我其实不相信他们会相信我们。
- We totally took it too far!
- 我们真的做得太过分了！
- Maybe we should've told the truth.
- 也许我们应该说实话。
- Ugh. [toy squeaking]
- 哎呀。
If we bail now, you get detention,
如果我们现在离开，你会被留堂，
you get no re-test, and you get no Taylie!
你无法重考，而且你也得不到泰莉！
So start selling this thing!
所以开始推销这个东西吧！
[all barking]
[众狗吠叫]
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
- [sighs]
[叹气]
I'm sad we're not with our little girl right now.
我现在很难过，没能和我们的小女儿在一起。
- I know. I feel like I haven't seen her
我知道。我感觉好像已经有一个小时没见到她了。
in, like, an hour. - Oh, she's gotta be so nervous.
哦，她一定很紧张。
- Terrified. She's all alone. - Without us.
吓坏了。她孤零零的。- 没有我们陪伴。
I mean, don't you think she would want us with her?
我的意思是，你不觉得她会希望我们陪着她吗？
- Oh, I'm sure she would, Anne,
哦，我肯定她会的，安妮，
but I've been calling for her and whistling for her.
但我一直在呼唤她，吹口哨召唤她。
I even made her this cute little outfit.
我甚至还为她做了这件可爱的小衣服。
- Who are you talking about?
你在说谁？
- Denise. Who are you talking about?
丹尼斯。你在说谁？
- Our daughter,
我们的女儿，
who is singing her first solo today without us!
今天她要第一次独自唱独唱，没有我们在场！
- Oh. Right. Pretty cute, though, huh?
哦。对。不过挺可爱的，对吧？
- [sighs] I'm leaving, Tom.
我要走了，汤姆。
- What? Over this?
什么？就因为这个？
This is nowhere near the worst thing I've ever done!
这远不是我做过的最糟糕的事！
- For the benefit.
为了大家的利益。
- Oh. Right.
哦，对。
Me too! [laughs] Let's go, Squish.
我也是！[笑] 走吧，Squish。
I don't wanna lose two dogs
我不想一天之内失去两条狗，
and almost your mother in one day.
还差点失去你妈妈。
[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
- Thank you.
谢谢你。
- You're too kind.
你太客气了。
- [blubbering]
- [抽泣]
- We're monsters!
- 我们是怪物！
- Hold it together!
- 控制住情绪！
You're an angel.
你是个天使。
- We're devils!
- 我们是恶魔！
- [exhales] Okay.
- [叹气] 好吧。
It's almost showtime.
快到表演时间了。
- Attention, everyone!
- 大家注意！
As co-chairs of the student body boosters,
作为学生会促进会的联合主席，
we just wanted to thank you all for coming out today
我们只想感谢大家今天能来
and for your generous donations of love.
以及你们慷慨的爱心捐赠。
[applause] - Okay. It's almost showtime.
好的。演出即将开始。
- But before Dawn sings, let's welcome
但在Dawn唱歌之前，让我们欢迎
some neighborhood children who have come
一些邻家的小朋友们，他们来到这里
to literally open their piggy banks
实际上是为了打开他们的存钱罐
all in the name of Squishy.
全都是为了Squishy。
Kids!
孩子们！
- [exhales] - Steady, boys.
稳住，小伙子们。
- We've done some selfish things before, but this...
我们以前做过一些自私的事情，但这次...
- Here you go. It's my life savings.
给你。这是我全部的积蓄。
- [wheezing]
- [喘气]
- This is rock bottom!
- 这是最低谷了！
- No, it's not.
- 不，不是。
- This is my best friend.
- 这是我的好朋友。
I call him, Bobby.
我叫他，鲍比。
I want Squishy to have it.
我想让Squishy拥有它。
- [gasps] This is.
- [惊呼] 这是。
- Beautiful.
- 美丽。
Let's give it up for Josephine and Grayson,
让我们为Josephine和Grayson鼓掌，
Principal Noonan's kids.
Principal Noonan的孩子们。
- Correction.
更正。
[applause]
掌声
- Dawn Harper is going to now sing a song of pure joy.
现在由Dawn Harper演唱一首充满喜悦的歌曲。
You're so brave.
你真勇敢。
- Thank you, everyone. [sighs]
谢谢大家。[叹气]
This goes out to all of you.
这是献给你们所有人的。
And Squishy.
还有Squishy。
[gentle piano music]
轻柔的钢琴音乐
- [whispering] Hi!
嗨！
- Squishy?
Squishy？
[together] Squishy!
[一起] 斯奎西！
all: Squishy?
所有人: 斯奎西？
- [growling, barking]
- [咆哮，吠叫]
[all gasp]
[所有人倒吸一口气]
[crowd gasps]
[人群倒吸一口气]
- Denise!
- 丹尼斯！
- Well, the good news is, Squishy is all right.
- 好消息是，斯奎西没事。
So hit it, Ms. T!
所以开始吧，T女士！
And a one, and a two, and a three--
一，二，三——
[gasps] - I knew it was a quad thing!
[倒吸一口气] - 我就知道这是四重奏的事！
- She knew it was a quad thing!
她知道那是四人组的事！
[rock music]
摇滚音乐
- So, after a full day of dog washing,
那么，经过一整天的洗狗活动，
do you think you kids have finally learned your lesson?
你们这些孩子觉得自己终于学到教训了吗？
[together] Yes.
是的。
- We have. - We will never again
我们学到了。
play on people's sympathies just to get what we want.
我们再也不会利用人们的同情心来得到我们想要的东西。
- No more big, fat quad things.
不再有那些大而肥的四人组事情。
- You don't have to say "big, fat."
你不必说“大而肥”。
- Just quad things.
只是四人组的事情。
- So I guess we're done.
所以我想我们结束了。
- Not yet!
还没呢！
Khaleesi needs a bath.
卡丽熙需要洗个澡。
- We're gonna need a bigger sponge.
我们需要一个更大的海绵。
- [barks]
汪！
- Oh! - Ugh!
哦！
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
呃！
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
[whistling]
♪ ♪
口哨声
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪